<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on BL Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://lipovski.ca/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on BL Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lipovski.ca/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Healthcare Liasion Officer: An Intervention Framework to Promote Health and Huamnity within Canada&#39;s Federal Carceral System</title>
      <link>https://lipovski.ca/blogs/spph481c_finalpaper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lipovski.ca/blogs/spph481c_finalpaper/</guid>
      <description>Literature Review Since the introduction of the 1984 Canada Health Act, Canadians have enjoyed the benefits of universal medicade; however, the same cannot be said for its prison population [1]. Although there is disagreement about how those who break the rules should be punished, there is little discourse on the basic human rights of individuals who are incarcerated [1,2]. Simply put, the most vocal voices that argue for more intense criminal punishments often have little or no first-hand account of the day-to-day experiences of those serving time [1].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inclusivity &amp; the Olympic Athlete: A Case Study of Foekje Dillema</title>
      <link>https://lipovski.ca/blogs/kin364_midtermpaper/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lipovski.ca/blogs/kin364_midtermpaper/</guid>
      <description>Foekje Dillema © Nationaal Archief, used under CC BY-SA 3.0 nl
1. Introduction Sport is a ubiquitous social institution within almost every recorded society (Frey &amp;amp; Eitzen, 1991; Suter, 2009). As such, its universality insinuates a great potential to uphold the dignity of humanity (Frey &amp;amp; Eitzen, 1991; Washington &amp;amp; Karen, 2001). However, sport is itself a social phenomenon deeply woven into the frameworks of society (International Olympic Committee, 2020; Schut, 2018; Washington &amp;amp; Karen, 2001.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
